I want to speak to your life now. When you receive it with all your heart, you are free.
Are you ready?
Right now, talk to yourself. You can talk to yourself because a doubter is a double-minded person.
He's here; he's outside. I don't want you to be a doubter.
Remember what you said - stop doubting and believe.
Talk to yourself.
Here is the grace. Here is the hour.
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are, whatever you are doing at this moment,
distance is not a barrier. Just hear the Word and be under the influence.
Agree with me - Jesus loves you.
I say, "Agree with me - Jesus loves me".
You know Jesus loves you and He is concerned about you.
He wants to be involved.
If you allow Him to be involved as a mother, testimony is next.
Hallelujah.
Right now, whatever wall between you and God Almighty,
whatever weaknesses or unrighteousness...
You know yourself. As we are talking, something is telling you,
"Will God answer my prayer?" - because you know where you are coming from.
But Jesus never consults our past to determine our future.
He never consults our past to determine our present.
That is Jesus. He loves you; He is concerned about you.
He never consults our past.
It's only satan that has that information about our past and he's using it against us.
But Jesus never consults your past to determine your present.
Put it behind you. Love Him; He loves you.
Yes.
Every spirit, all unclean spirits operating in your life -
listen to that.
All unclean spirits operating in your life -
be it in your career, health, marriage, family, finances, business -
all unclean spirits operating in your life, I command them to leave you right now!
Right now, release yourself. Begin to command all unclean spirits operating in your life to leave you!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
Let me prepare you.
I will leave you to talk. Let me get you there.
Unclean spirit is the cause and is behind those pains, that complaining.
He is responsible.
He leads people to do shameless acts.
You have been praying that you don't want to do this, and you keep finding yourself doing them.
And these are the things that are giving you trouble.
Each time you want to talk to God, you feel, "Ah, will God hear my prayer?"
because of what happened to you.
He uses all that unrighteousness, evil, sin, weaknesses -
he is using them to operate in your life.
Through those unrighteous things, he enters to operate.
These are the foolish things we are talking about.
All unclean spirits operating in your life, causing chains,
that satan is using to connect you to himself -
he is using those things to connect you to himself -
those are the chains he is using to connect you to himself, to operate and strike.
All unclear spirits operating in your life -
I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
You know those things satan is using to operate in your life.
It could be that you talk too much. You know those acts.
Satan uses them as a chain to connect himself.
When he connects himself to you, he will now begin to drag you, drag you, drag you.
Open your lips now.
Every unclean spirit operating in your life - declare them wanted right now!
In the name of Jesus, unclean spirits operating in your life, command them out!
Say, Out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Viewers all over the world!
In the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, we want you to follow us.
Distance is not a barrier; where you are is not a barrier.
Where are you? Follow us!
You just need to be under the influence of what we are doing here.
All unclean spirits operating in your life, operating in your health,
operating in your business, operating in your career,
operating in your marriage, operating in your family,
operating in your life,
declare them right now, wanted!
I command them out!
Leave my people!
Leave my people, you unclean spirit!
Jesus healed every infirmity.
Sickness, disease, every infirmity, submit to Jesus!
I command that infirmity, that sickness and disease, satan's curse,
I command you out, in the name of Jesus!
Out from your blood!
Begin to command them out!
You sickness and disease - infirmity, you affliction in the blood - infirmity,
you affliction in the bones - infirmity, you affliction in the liver - infirmity,
you affliction in the kidneys - infirmity, you affliction in the blood - infirmity, out!
Out!
You affliction, leave my people!
Leave their blood! Leave their kidneys!
Leave their liver! Leave their bones!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever that affliction is located, leave, in the name of Jesus!
I say, Leave, in the name of Jesus!
Leave, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Never a sickness Jesus cannot cure. Cure them, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Within and outside, cure them, in the name of Jesus!
Within and without, cure them, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
That affliction is healed!
That affliction is removed!
In Jesus Christ's name.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Confess your healing! Confess your liberty!
If there is anyone who is still under the dominion of satan, I declare freedom, in the name of Jesus!
Freedom to you, in the name of Jesus!
Freedom for you, in the name of Jesus!
The way out for you has come!
Say to yourself: The way out for me has come, in Jesus' name!
The way out for my life has come!
Freedom! Freedom! To you - freedom!
Overflow Congregation
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Watch your screen.
You can see demons manifesting and people already abide under the influence of this prayer right now.
Anywhere you are, touch your screen.
As demons are manifesting in people, people are also vomiting in different parts of the church
poisonous substances from their system.
Continue to pray.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen.
You can see the blood substance in what that man is vomiting.
That is the poisonous substance in his system he is vomiting right now as the prayer is going on.
What have you done to her as a king?
I have been there for ages.
I told you that I'm a strong man!
In the mother's house!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am a king!
From the marine world!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am the giant man! Finish!
Stagnation in her career!
Miscarriages!
She is a teacher, a high-school teacher.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
When did you enter her?
From birth.
Who is this man?
This one says he is her husband. I have dealt with him!
She's my wife.
She is very very violent, very very stubborn. She doesn't listen to advice.
She is always very angry with the children. She is always molesting the children in the house.
She has a very hot temper that always makes us...
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
You know unclean spirits submit to the name of Jesus. Do you know this?
If you call this name with all your heart, unclean spirits submit to the name.
When I say, "All unclean spirits operating in your life",
we do not expect any unclean spirits in your surroundings again,
if you call this name with all your heart.
There is wonderful name Jesus
There is no other name I know
Every organ in your body - begin to function, in the name of Jesus!
Every organ that is not functioning, I command them to begin to function, in the name of Jesus!
Any organ in your system that is not functioning -
I command them to begin to function, in the name of Jesus!
Be it in your liver, kidney, bone, blood - I command them to function, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to function, in the name of Jesus!
Prayer!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Who are you?
I am a giant man!
What have you done to her?
I have destroyed her career!
Her marriage?
She doesn't love that man!
How did you enter her?
Through dream!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Who are you? What have you done to him?
You are troubling me!
Who are you?
I told you I'm the spiritual wife.
What have you done to him? What have you pushed him to do?
I have pushed him to fornicate.
Why?
He refused to marry me. That's why.
What have you done to his career?
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I command any pain in your system to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
You affliction, leave my people!
Your body is the temple of the Holy Ghost.
Leave my people!
Affliction, leave my people!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Rejoice!
I know my people!
Viewers, begin to rejoice!
Rejoice for your healing!
I'm healed! Your declaration will be granted!
I can't hear you.
I'm healed!
In Jesus' name.
Right now, confess your healing in the light of your healing.
I am healed!
The way out for you has come.
Say to yourself, "The way out for me has come, in Jesus' name!"
The way out for my life has come.
If the way out for you has come, what else again? This is the promise of God.
Give thanks to Him. The way out for me has come.
It means Someone is somewhere planning for you - Jesus Christ!
Say, Someone is planning for me! The way out for me has come.
With Him, all things are possible. In Jesus Christ's name.
Right now, remember your nation in prayer, your country in prayer
and those nations that are in a trouble zone.
Remember them in prayer.
Hallelujah. Open your lips. Ask for God's intervention.
God's intervention.
Prayer For the Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
God's intervention.
Prayer For the Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Begin to search your hearts.
Hear from your heart.
Am I free?
You can hear this voice, if you are not a double person.
If you are here with all your heart, you can hear this, "Am I free?"
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Freedom from God is freedom indeed!
I can hear freedom!
If you cannot hear, I'm hearing freedom!
I know my people. Am I talking to you?
Those who are here, listen! I can hear freedom!
Freedom!
In Jesus Christ's name.
I cover you with the blood of Jesus.
Be covered by the blood of Jesus!
My hands are blessed with the blessings of the Lord
Anything I touch surely must be blessed
My hands are filled with the blessings of the Lord
Right now, open your lips and begin to fix everything that has to do with you.
In the name of Jesus, fix your business and career before you leave here finally.
Whatever you fix is fixed.
Begin to fix your career, business, marriage and family. Fix them, in the name of Jesus!
Don't forget to fix the issues of your nation. Fix them!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.